Guide to the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South Records, 1939-2018 RL.01081
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South records
1939-2018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, Inc.
RL.01081
33.5 Linear Feet
A non-profit organization, located in Durham, N.C., founded in 1977 for the purpose of providing support for women in ministry, persons of faith working for justice in the South, and religious organizations that address women's needs. The records are relevant to the study of the relationships among religion, politics, and society, particularly how women in ministry have confronted a number of social issues facing the South. Information pertaining to the Equal Rights Amendment, sexism, economic justice and poverty, gays and lesbians in the Church, feminism, abortion, racism, and rural ministry is included. Also includes materials on retreats and conferences, some organized by the Resource Center, which focused on many of the issues above and other concerns, including gender and language, spirituality, medical care, housing and homelessness, women in ministry, and women in the workplace.
33.5 linear feet
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South Records were donated to the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 1991 and 1992. Additional materials have been donated in subsequent years, including 1994, 1995, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006, 2007, 2008, 2009, 2011-2012, 2014-2015, and 2018.
Historical Note
1977, Aug. Incorporated as a nonprofit organization. Jeanette Stokes was listed as the incorporator and a trustee. Helen G. Crotwell and Sue Parkerson were also named as trustees
1977, Nov. Tax exempt status approved by the Internal Revenue Service
1978 Began publishing South of the Garden, newsletter for the organization. Issued for one year at no charge
1979 Began selling subscriptions to South of the Garden
1982 Women in Ministry in North Carolina conferences begun
1984 Women, Faith and Economic Justice conferences begun
1984 Keeping Yourself Together While Changing the World conferences begun
1986 Women in Ministry in the Virginias conferences begun
1991 Published brochure, Investment That Counts: A Guide to Socially Responsible Investing for People of Faith
Collection Overview
The records of the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South span the years 1939 to 2018 with the bulk occurring from 1977 to 1990. The Resource Center's mission of working for justice in the South as well as its operations are reflected in the records, which primarily consist of printed material, correspondence, writings, clippings, account books, grant proposals, minutes, newsletters, photographs, audio tapes, filmstrips, and videocassette tapes.
The Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South Records are especially relevant to the study of the relationships among religion, politics and society. In particular they document how women, especially women in ministry, have confronted a number of social issues facing the South as well as the entire United States. Information pertaining to the Equal Rights Amendment, sexism, feminism, economic justice and poverty, gays and lesbians in the Church, Central America, child abuse, abortion and the abortion controversy, racism, and rural ministry is included in the records. Information on these issues as well as others is contained in the Alphabetical Files and Printed Material series. Retreats and conferences, some organized by the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, which focus on many of the above issues as well as other concerns, including gender and language, spirituality, housing and homelessness, women in ministry, health and medical care, and women in the workplace are reflected in the Alphabetical Files, Audiovisual, and Pictures series. Many of these retreats and conferences were held in North Carolina and Virginia. In the Printed Material Series, are copies of South of the Garden, a newsletter published by the Resource Center, resource packets pertaining to sexism and ministries to women in crisis among other subjects, and a number of religious newsletters that focus on women in the Church.
The records reflect the ecumenical vision of the Resource Center in that the major Protestant denominations are represented in the records. Within these denominations, women's organizations are the primary focus, including the Presbyterian Committee on Women's Concerns, the National Association of Presbyterian Clergy Women, and the United Church of Christ Clergywomen's Conference. Other religious bodies and organizations reflected in the records include the North Carolina Council of Churches - Committee for ERA, Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights, and programs for women at the University of North Carolina at Greensboro. Material pertaining to these organizations are primarily located in the Alphabetical Files; Financial Papers; Meetings, Conferences, and Workshops; and Printed Material series.
Significant individuals reflected in the records, primarily within the Audiovisual Series, include Rosemary Radford Ruether, Anne Wilson Schaef, Katie Cannon, and Carter Heyward. The correspondence, writings, sermons and addresses, and notes of Jeanette Stokes, Director of the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, are chiefly contained in the Financial Papers; Meetings, Conferences, and Workshops; and Audiovisual series. Documents concerning the operations and history of the Resource Center, including account books, grant proposals, and incorporation materials are primarily located in the Financial Papers and Miscellaneous Series.
Poverty; Racism; Sexism -- United States; Rural clergy -- Southern States; Social problems; Medical care; Religion and justice; Homelessness -- United States; Equal rights amendment; Religion and politics -- United States; Women and religion -- Southern States; Women clergy -- Southern States; Spirituality; Feminism; Homosexuality -- Religious aspects; Lesbianism -- Religious aspects; Women, Presbyterian; Cannon, Katie G.; Heyward, Carter; Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South. South of the Garden; University of North Carolina at Greensboro; Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, Inc.; Ruether, Rosemary Radford; Schaef, Anne Wilson; Stokes, Jeanette; Mattern, Evelyn
- Alphabetical Files Series, 1939-1991 and undated (bulk 1977-1990)
  Scope and Contents note
  Primarily consists of printed material, correspondence, clippings, photographs, and writings. This series reflects some of the primary activities of the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South. Included are programs and lecture notes from the various conferences that were organized by the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South; and minutes of meetings for the North Carolina Council of Churches--Committee for ERA, and the National Abortion Rights Action League - North Carolina. Other organizations represented in this series include the Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights, the Guilford Women's Network, and the National Association of Presbyterian Clergywomen. Also includes resource materials on various social concerns, including racism, child abuse, and economic justice. Arranged alphabetically by topic and chronologically within folders.
  - Abortion: (Box 1)
    - 1980-1990, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Anti-abortion, 1980-1985 (Box 1)
    - Clippings, 1979-1990 (Box 1)
    - Guilford Coalition for Choice, 1981-1983 (Box 1)
    - National Abortion Rights Action League--North Carolina, 1980-1986 (Box 1)
    - Religious perspectives, 1977-1989, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Bible and Women, 1963-1983 (Box 1)
  - Bible:
    - New Testament, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Old Testament, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Bibliographies, 1973-1985, undated, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Blacks, 1983-1988 (Box 1)
  - Black Women, 1979-1987, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Brown, Antionette, project, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Campus Ministry Women, 1986, Aug. (Box 1)
  - Center for Corporate Responsibility and similar efforts, 1974-1983 (Box 1)
  - Center for Women's Economic Alternatives, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Central America, 1982-1989 (Box 1)
  - Children: Child abuse, 1979-1987 (Box 1)
  - Commissions on Women, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Easter, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Economic Justice:
    - Poverty and women, 1984-1989, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Social security, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - Status of women in U.S., 1979-1986, undated (Box 1)
    - Women's Commission in Exile (later named Women for Economic Justice), 1981-1988 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, A-Z, 1980-1985 (Box 1)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1980-1984, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Evangelical Women's Caucus, 1979-1983 (Box 2)
  - Gay/Lesbian Issues, 1980-1989, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Gay/Lesbian Issues and Religion, 1975-1988, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Greensboro Area Women in Ministry, 1983-1984, undated (Box 2)
  - Guilford Women's Network, 1980-1989, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Health, 1977-1989 (Box 2)
  - History of Women in the Southern Conference, (UCC) (United Church of Christ) Slide show, 1942-1981 (Box 2)
  - Housing: 1984-1989, 3 folders
    - Women, Faith, and Housing Conference, 1989, April 7-8 (Box 2)
  - Keeping Yourself Together conference, 1984, Oct. 1987, 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1980-1986 (Box 2)
  - Language, 1974-1989, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Marketing, 1982-1989, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Nairobi (Non-governmental Organization Forum, 1985) (Box 3)
  - National Association of Presbyterian Clergywomen (See: Presbyterian Clergywomen, National Association of, 1981-1990) (Box 3)
  - North Carolina Council of Churches--Committee for ERA, 1979-1985, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Peace, 1981-1985, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - People:
    - Amidei, Nancy, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Bentley, Sarah, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Bernard, Carol, 1980-1988 (Box 3)
    - Goin, Mary Elizabeth (1939-1987), 1985-1987 (Box 3)
    - Maynard, Jeannine, 1977-1981 (Box 3)
    - Pearce, B. J., undated (Box 3)
    - Ruether, Rosemary Radford, 1979-1987 (Box 3)
    - Tennis, Diane, 1974-1986 (Box 3)
    - Way, Peggy, undated (Box 3)
  - Politics:
    - 1980-1988 (Box 3)
    - New Right:
      - 1980-1985 (Box 3)
      - Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 3)
  - Presbyterian Clergywomen, National Association of: Survey, 1981-1990 (Box 3)
  - Presbyterian Committee on Women's Concerns (COWC), 1976-1981 (Box 3)
  - Racism, 1978-1985 (Box 3)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights (See: Abortion Religious Perspectives, 1977-1989) (Box 3)
  - Rural Ministry:
    - Resource book on women in rural ministry, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
    - Resources, 1978-1980 (Box 3)
    - Seminar, 1979, Oct. 2-4; 1981, May (Box 3)
  - Sexuality, 1981-1987 (Box 3)
  - Taxes, 1981-1986 (Box 3)
  - United Church of Christ and Women, 1977-1984 (Box 3)
  - United Church of Christ Clergywomen's Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - United Church of Christ National Meeting of Women for Leadership Development, 1979 (Box 4)
  - United Church of Christ, Southern Regional meeting, 1979, Oct. 11-13 (Box 4)
  - United Methodist Church (Box 4)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro:
    - Presbyterian House, 1979-1984 (Box 4)
    - Programs for women at UNC-G, 1980-1987 (Box 4)
    - Women's Resource Center, 1981-1984 (Box 4)
    - Women faculty bag lunches, 1983-1985 (Box 4)
  - Women, Faith and Economic Justice Conference, 1984, Nov.; 1990, Mar., 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Women, Faith, and Health Care Justice Conference, 1988, Mar. 25-26 (Box 4)
  - Women, Faith, and Public Policy Conference, 1980, Apr. 11-12, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Women Faith, and Tax Justice Conference, Raleigh, N.C., 1991, Mar. 15-16, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Women in ministry:
    - 1977-1990 (Box 4)
    - Clippings, 1977-1990 (Box 4)
    - N.C. Conference, 1982, May 16-1988, May, 8 folders (Box 4)
    - North Carolina Conference, 1989, May 14-1990, May 27-29, 4 folders (Box 5)
    - Browns Summit, N.C., 1991, May 26-28, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Virginia Conference, 1986-1990, Oct. 21-23, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Women's Equality Day, 1980-1983, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Women's stores and companies, 1983-1985 (Box 5)
  - Women's Theological Center, Boston, Mass., 1982-1989 (Box 5)
  - Worship and liturgy, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
- Financial Papers Series, 1973-1991 and undated (bulk 1978-1989)
  Includes account books and receipts documenting the financial operation of the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South. Also includes requests for outside funding and grant applications to various denominational organizations and other institutions. Financial information pertaining to the Resource Center is arranged chronologically at the beginning of the series, then alphabetically. Requests for funding are arranged in alphabetical order by fund name.
  - 1983, undated (Box 5)
  - Account books: Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, 1977, Aug.?1988, July (3 vols.) (Box 5)
  - Account books: Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, 1978, Aug. - 1988, Aug.(4 folders and 1 vol.) (Box 6)
  - Accounting, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Budget, 1983-1990 (Box 6)
  - Funding:
    - Anderson Foundation, 1979 (Box 6)
    - Church Women United, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
    - First Presbyterian Church (Durham, N.C.) Service and Mission Committee, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Joint Foundation Support, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 6)
    - Kentucky Foundation for Women, Inc., 1987 (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Baptist Hospital School of Pastoral Care Foundation, 1982-1986 (Box 6)
    - North Carolina Humanities Committee, 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Orange Presbytery Hunger Committee, 1986 (Box 6)
    - St. Mary's House (UNC-Greensboro ), 1986-1987 (Box 6)
    - United Methodist Church Commission on Religion and Race, 1979-1983 (Box 6)
    - United Methodist Church Women's Division Assembly Offering, 1978 (Box 6)
    - United Methodist Women's Call to Prayer and Self-Denial Offering, 1985-1988 (Box 6)
    - United Presbyterian Church in the USA Experimental and Emergency Program Grants, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
    - United Thank Offering, 1986-1989 (Box 6)
    - Windom Fund, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Women of the Evangelical Lutheran Church in America/Lutheran Church Women, 1984-1988 (Box 6)
    - Women's Opportunity Giving Fund, 1984-1988 (Box 6)
    - Z. Smith Reynolds Foundation: 1979-1987 (Box 6)
    - Women, Faith, and Housing Project, 1985-1989 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1987 (Box 6)
  - Receipts, 1982-1985, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Socially Responsible Investing and Fundraising, 1989-1991 (Box 6)
- Meetings, Conferences, and Workshops Series, 1978-1988
  Contains printed material; writings; minutes from meetings; lecture and seminar notes; and correspondence related to meetings, conferences, or workshops in which Jeanette Stokes participated. The materials are not directly related to the seminars and conferences organized by the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South; these are documented in the Alphabetical Files Series. Arranged alphabetically.
  - American Academy of Religion/Society of Biblical Literature Annual Meeting, Dallas, 1983, Dec. 19-22 (Box 6)
  - Appalachian State University, Association of Women Students, Boone, N.C. 1981, Nov. 17-18 (Box 6)
  - Asheville United Church of Christ Women's Fellowship, Asheville, N.C., 1980, Mar. 8 (Box 6)
  - Church Women United, Burlington, N.C., 1981, Oct. 3 (Box 6)
  - Church Women United Executive Staff Conference, 1979, Jan. 16-18 (Box 6)
  - Church Women United in North Carolina, Southern Pines, N.C. 1981, Mar. 13-14 (Box 6)
  - Consultation of Ethnic Minority Women in Ministry, Washington, D.C., 1978, Apr. 20-23 (Box 6)
  - First Presbyterian Church:
    - Greensboro, N.C., 1981, Nov. 9 (Box 6)
    - High Point, NC., 1980, May 5 (Box 6)
  - Leadership Training Day, Cincinnati, 1988, Feb. 20 (Box 7)
  - Meet the Funders Forum, 1981, May 6 (Box 7)
  - North Carolina Women's Conference, Montreat, N.C., 1980, June 12-15 (Box 7)
  - North Carolina Women's Forum, Greensboro, N.C., 1984, Jan. 14 (Box 7)
  - Outstanding American Church Women, Burlington, NC., 1979, Oct. (Box 7)
  - Presbyterian Commission on Women's Concerns (COWC) Workshop, Atlanta, Ga., 1980, Nov. 22 (Box 7)
  - Seminar on Religion, Justice, and the Equal Rights Amendment, Winston-Salem, N.C., 1980, Mar. 20 (Box 7)
  - Theology and Power, Intentional Growth Center, Lake Junaluska, N.C., 1981, Apr. 2-4 (Box 7)
  - Tri-Synod Women's Consultation, Wirtz, Va., 1986, Mar. 7-9 (Box 7)
  - Tryon Presbyterian Church, Tryon, N.C., 1980, Oct. 27 (Box 7)
  - Upper Piedmont Women in Ministry, Easley, S.C., 1979 (Box 7)
  - Using Our Gifts, 1984, Mar., June (Box 7)
  - Women in Ministry, N.C. Memorial Hospital, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1986, Jan. 20 (Box 7)
  - Women of the Church Retreat, First Presbyterian Church, Greensboro, N.C., 1979, May 6-7 (Box 7)
  - Women's Forum of North Carolina, Asheville, N.C., 1980, Oct. 4 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1981 (Box 7)
- Printed Material Series, 1956-1992 and undated (bulk 1970-1990)
  Includes brochures for conferences organized by the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, religious newsletters, issues of South of the Garden, and surveys directed at readers of South of the Garden. Also contains resource packets concerning issues related to women in ministry, study guides, and correspondence pertaining to South of the Garden. The first part of the series is arranged chronologically. The remainder is chiefly arranged alphabetically by title. Issues of South of the Garden follow the newsletters.
  - 1973-1981, undated, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Brochures: Conferences sponsored by Resource Center, 1984-1992 (Box 7)
  - Greeting cards/fundraising, 1983-1992 (Box 7)
  - Newsletters:
    - Called and Committed (SBC), 1978-1979 (Box 7)
    - Campus Ministry Women Newsletter, 1988-1990 (Box 7)
    - The Church Woman, 1986-1987 (Box 7)
    - The Common Lot (UCC), 1987-1989 (Box 7)
    - The Corporate Examiner, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Daughters of Clara (CC, Disciples), 1985-1987 (Box 7)
    - Ecumenical Women's Center Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
    - The Flyer (UMC), 1987-1990 (Box 7)
    - Friends of Hagar, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Journal of Women and Religion/Center for Women and Religion Membership Newsletter, 1987-1990 (Box 7)
    - Journal of Women's Ministries (Episcopal), 1988 (Box 7)
    - Placement Happens When..., 1979-1981 (Box 7)
    - Quickenings, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Ruach (Episcopal), 1987-1990 (Box 7)
    - The Shibboleth (UMC), 1984-1985 (Box 7)
    - The Sojourner, 1977-1986 (Box 7)
    - Southern Baptists for the Family and Equal Rights, 1981-1985 (Box 7)
    - Watchword/Claiming Our Gifts (ABC), 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Waves, 1983-1985 (Box 7)
    - Women's Concerns (United Church of Canada), 1984-1988 (Box 7)
    - Women's Network News/The Well Woman (Lutheran), 1988-1990 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1990 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous: Subscriptions, 1978-1984 (Box 7)
  - South of the Garden and South of the Garden Books catalogs, 1978-1990, undated (Box 8)
  - South of the Garden: (Box 9)
  - Goofs, 1984-1987
    - Readers' Survey, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Responses, 1978-1991 (Box 9)
  - Study guides, 1975-1979 (Box 9)
  - Resource packets:
    - Human Rights of Women, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Ministries with Women in Crisis, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Racism/Sexism: A Resource Packet for Leaders, 1979, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Sexism, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Study on the Community of Women and Men in the Church, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Theology in the Americas Women's Project, 1977-1980 (Box 9)
    - The Woman Packet, 1970-1974 (Box 9)
    - Women Choosing--Women Growing, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Women: Partners in Ministry, 1956-1982 (Box 9)
    - Women's Sampler, 1970-1975 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982, undated (Box 9)
- Audiovisual Series, 1974-1990 and undated
  Contains videocassette tapes, audio tapes, filmstrips, and printed material relating to the audiovisual media. Included are sermons and addresses, including those given at conferences organized by the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South. Arranged chronologically. Numbers below correspond to those on the audiovisual material folders.
  - Case 1
    - 1974:"Out of the Garden," Dorie Ellzey (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 1977, Summer:Jeanette Stokes, Duke Chapel (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 1979, Jan. 11-12:Meditations by Barbara Gerlach, Murdale Leysath, UCC National Women's Meeting (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 1979:"Impact on Public Policy" (with filmstrip), (See kit folders) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 1980:"Women Together" (with filmstrip), (See kit folders) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 1981, Nov. 9:Public Affairs Workshop (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 1983, Oct. 26:Mary Kay Wakeman and Jeanette Stokes, "Women, Power, and Spirituality," Association of Women Students, UNC-Greensboro (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 1983, October 31 - November 2:Mr. Carnevale, Ms. Lloyd, Ms. McCabel, "Women as Producers," Governor's Conference on Women and the Economy (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 1983, October 31 - November 2:Ms. Jeffrey, Ms. Norton, "Women in the Workplace," Governor's Conference on Women and the Economy (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 1984, Jan. 14:Jeanette Stokes, N.C. Women's Forum (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 1984, Feb. 15: susan B. Anthony Day (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 1984 May 13-14:Anne Wilson Schaef, Women in Ministry Retreat Sessions I-II (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 1984, May 14:Anne Schaef, Women in Ministry Retreat Sessions II-III (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Case 2
    - 1984, May 14:Anne Schaef, Women in Ministry Retreat Session III (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 1984, July 12-16:"Women in the Spirit: Called and Free," 2nd National Meeting, UCC Women (with filmstrip), (See kit folders) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - 1984, Nov. 16-17:"Women, Faith and Economic Justice" (Located in audiocassette Case 5) (Folder 15a-e)
      - 1984, Nov. 16:Panel 1, Feminization of Poverty (Box 9, Folder 15a)
      - 1984, Nov. 17:Panel 2, The Best Ones to Tell It are the Ones Who Live It (Box 9, Folder 15b)
      - 1984, Nov. 17:Panel 3, Analysis (Box 9, Folder 15c)
      - 1984, Nov. 17:Two panels (Box 9, Folder 15d-e)
    - 1985, April 21:Jeanette Stokes, sermon, Sunday AM service, Princeton (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - 1985, Nov. 15-16:"Women, Faith, and Economic Justice" (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - 1987, Mar. 3:Jeanette Stokes and J. Knoop, Astrology (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 1987, Mar. 26:Women, Faith, and Economic Justice: Abu-Saba, Holmes, Hargrave (sides 5-6) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - 1987, Apr. 26:Margot Adler, Chants (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - 1987, June 1:Rosemary Ruether, Women in Ministry, N.C. Conference (sides 1-2) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - 1987, June 1:Rosemary Ruether, Women in Ministry, N.C. Conference (sides 3-4) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - 1987, June 2:Rosemary Ruether, Women in Ministry, N.C. Conference (sides 5-6) (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - 1987, June 2:Rosemary Ruether, Women in Ministry, N.C. Conference (side 7) (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - 1988, Mar. 26:Women, Faith, and Health Care Justice Conference (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Case 3
    - 1988, Mar. 26:Women, Faith, and Health Care Justice Conference (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference (sides 1-2) (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference (sides 3-4) (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - 1989, Apr, 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference: Rural Housing (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith and Housing Conference: Cushing Dolbeare (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference: Workshop: Senior Citizens (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference: Cushing Dolbeare (Box 10, Folder 32)